=Dungeon Archive=
The killer of the case is...
Jin Goofy.
(Killer of the case)
Longdong Army!
(Killer failed to escape)
(Jin Goofy)
(Case reconstruction)
I am the killer of the case, Jin Goofy.
(Talent Hub)
In this company,
me and my brother
were tortured by Tui Haowan.
We couldn't avoid
or escape.
The only way is to kill him
to start a new life.
(Year 2026)
On 21 June, 3PM,
I overheard Tui Haowan
sending a voice message
to his subordinate,
Bu Kakao, in his office
to kill someone.
It gave me a chance to kill him.
(22 June 2026. Crazy animal party)
On 22 June, at the crazy animal party,
(Ghost story two: Who Can Help Me?)
Tui Haowan prepared
(Revenge)
his own severed limb
to drop it in front of us
at the sharing session
to make us think he was dismembered
and came to haunt us.
He would pull down
the main power breaker at 3PM
and have his men pretend
to be ghosts to scare us.
(Not everyone can see the UV markings)
One detail in the voice message
(Get the light and breaker key from my drawer)
caught my attention.
(Outstanding graduate. Name: Huo Xiyi)
Tui Haowan can see UV light
(UV light)
that requires spectral light to reveal.
The breaker labels were marked
with invisible UV ink
(Do not touch. Risk of electric shock)
only Tui Haowan can see.
(The left breaker is leaking)
He warned Tui Haowan to pull the right breaker.
(Touching it means death)
That it was dangerous.
I decided
to investigate the boss myself.
(Year 2026)
22 June, 2AM.
I sneaked into his office.
(Special spectral light)
In the second drawer,
I found the spectral light
and breaker key.
(Power distribution box)
I took them to the breaker.
After opening it,
I use the spectral light
and saw a label on the breaker saying,
"Do not touch. Risk of electric shock."
I remembered Bu Kakao telling Tui Haowan
(Main switch is to the right of the labeled one)
the controlling switch
was on the right of the labeled one.
(Leaking breaker. Main breaker)
So if I switched the labeled tag
with the blank tag,
Tui Haowan would mistake
the leaking breaker for the main switch
and be electrocuted.
(Tui Games Company. Ghost Stories)
He also planned
(Ghost story two: Who can help us?)
to scared us with the severed limb
(Revenge)
during the sharing session.
He had a way to convince everyone
to believe the limbs belonged to him.
Everyone would think
he was dismembered
during the sharing session.
That would give me
a perfect alibi.
I put my plan into motion.
(22 June 2026)
At 2:30AM,
(Leaking breaker. Main breaker)
I moved the breaker label to the right
and locked it up.
(Special spectral light)
In the dark, I returned the key
and spectral light to his office.
(Melt-Away)
I also took some Melt-Away from the janitor's room
and hid enough water
in the courtyard beforehand.
(3PM)
Tui Haowan wanted to cut the power at 3PM
and have someone pretend
to be a ghost to scare us.
I remembered the meeting room lockers
could only fit one person each.
Using that to my advantage,
I forged a document
(How to break "Who can help me?" myth)
on how to break the "Who can help me?" myth
and placed it inside.
That made everyone think
that hiding alone
in the locker with a pomelo leaf symbol
would protect them
from the scary ghosts.
To ensure I had full access
to the locker,
(Talent Hub)
I even stole the front desk remote
(Press to open corresponding door)
to control every locker door
(Night vision glasses)
and got a pair of night vision glasses.
Just to be safe,
I even practiced moving
from the meeting room
to the courtyard in the dark.
Ensuring I can complete the plan
within 10 minutes and return.
(Year 2026)
22 June, 2:30PM.
(Crazy animal theme party. Starts 2:30PM)
I joined the party as usual.
After the power was cut at 3PM,
Tui Haowan touched
the wrong breaker and died.
(Night vision glasses)
I put on the night vision glasses
and sneaked to the courtyard.
I poured the hidden water
(Melt-Away)
and Melt-Away into the water vat.
Then I placed Tui Haowan's body
into the vat.
I propped his head up
with a wooden board
to dissolve his limbs
using the Melt-Away.
Finally, I threw the breaker key
into the vat too.
(Press to open the corresponding door)
Then I threw the remote and night vision glasses
into the courtyard
where everyone would pass by.
After doing all that,
I calmly returned to my locker
in the meeting room
and stayed with everyone else.
(Crazy animal theme party)
Pretending I had never left.
Tui Haowan,
let all of this suffering end today.
(Jin Jing player log archive)
(Profile update. Jin Goofy.
Tui Games Company HR)
(At work, but gonna breakdown)
I am player, Jin Jing.
In this case,
I play Tui Games Company's HR,
Jin Goofy.
Today is the company's
monthly team-building event.
My colleagues and I
were sharing ghost stories
in the meeting room
when suddenly, a severed limb
fell from above.
I knew
the show was about to begin.
Ding and Ning confirmed
the severed limb belongs to Tui Haowan.
He branded it himself.
Of course I knew.
Because this was part
of Tui Haowan's plan.
After all these years at the company,
(Multiple resentments)
tormenting me was one thing,
(Wants to kill him)
but I couldn't accept
that he also tormented my brother.
He was evil and deserved to die.
So I killed him in the blackout.
Since the others also had a motive,
I had to do everything
(Picking apart everyone's statements)
to shift suspicion
(to clear her suspicion)
onto someone else.
I had to use everything
to clear my name.
After reading the autopsy report,
I pretended to analyze the case.
(Pretending to reconstruct the crime)
The killer cut off all four limbs
(Putting on an objective act)
and placed them in everyone's room
then dissolved the rest of the body.
Dissolve.
So I can confused everyone
about Tui Haowan's time of death.
Making them think
the crime was impossible.
Then Ke said the killer was him.
My silly little brother
volunteered to be the scapegoat.
During the first group meeting,
Ding suddenly said
the corpse seemed to be electrocuted.
Seems to be electrocuted.
(Real cause of death figured out)
His words
(Pretending to be surprised)
made me panic.
Luckily, no one
followed that lead.
In the mysterious zone,
we witnessed
how animals punished humans.
Just as the second ritual
was about to begin,
Bu Kakao suddenly whispered into my ear
to leave with him
if things got dangerous.
What did he mean?
Why are you talking to me?
I immediately distanced myself from him.
No matter what,
I couldn't let everyone
notice me.
So far,
(Assessing the situation)
I was still safe.
(Not under much suspicion)
Only when I saw the family photo
did I realize
we were actually humans.
And we'd once done things
that harmed animals.
We were doing these things.
Honestly,
after watching the video of our crimes,
I felt awful.
(Learned the truth from the clues)
We deserve this punishment.
(why Tui Haowan exploited them)
And Tui Haowan was an animal.
But he went against
the Animal Bureau's intentions
and killed us.
You all deserve to die.
During the case discussion,
I analyzed the process of the murder.
In the middle.
The one he wanted to touch.
As they began to suspect Nan,
I was relieved.
During the group discussion,
the killer was found
to use night vision glasses
and UV light,
so everyone ruled out Nan,
who had night vision,
and Ke, who could see UV light.
That left
only He Struggle and me.
Since we all visited the office,
(Suspected due to edge of profession)
everyone started suspecting me
(Trying to clear her name)
because of the edge of my profession.
That's the main thing.
I immediately shared my thoughts
(Arguing she had no clue)
to clear myself of suspicion.
(of Tui Haowan's plan
based on her job scope)
(Voting window)
During the final vote,
I knew I was in danger
because everyone thought
my motive was stronger.
So I voted for He Struggles
to increase the number of wrong votes.
(Zhang Linghe player log archive)
(Profile update. He Struggle)
(Tui Games Company
top motion caption actor)
(If you mess with me,
you've only kicked a cotton ball)
I am player Zhang Linghe.
In this case,
I play Tui Games Company's
top motion caption actor, He Struggle.
Today was
the company's monthly
crazy animal theme party.
I dressed up
as a capybara
in the event.
As we were sharing ghost stories,
...and limbs.
a severed limb fell from above.
Ding Staring recognized it.
It was the boss' leg.
This is the boss' leg.
Could something happen to him?
During the investigation,
we found all of his limbs
(This is)
covered in messages written in blood.
This is...
When pieced together,
it said,
"This is a revenge against humans."
(This is a revenge against humans)
From the clues, I discovered
my body and habits
were becoming more animal-like.
I was starting to grow capybara fur.
Capybara fur.
I also unconsciously act like an animal.
He seems to be experiencing this now.
(Realizing he's developed animal traits)
What was going on?
(Secretly wondering about the mutation)
After further investigation,
I discovered every suspect
had developed animal traits.
We speculated
(Analyzing killer's motive)
that an animal was abused
(based on severed limbs and mutation)
and planned this revenge.
The true identities
of the suspects
were most likely animals.
(Inferred everyone's true identity
based on clues on the limbs)
After that, we arrived
at the mysterious zone
and discovered a group of animals
gathering there.
They were there
to punish humans.
Who hurt your bodies?
But we weren't animals.
(The Mirror confirmed them as humans)
We were humans who harmed animals.
This place was a huge human prison
that locked humans
who had harmed animals.
They injected us
with animal transformation drugs
and tortured those we cared about.
(Through Animal Bureau's video,)
So we would feel the pain they suffered.
(discovered purpose of the hub)
They deserve this punishment.
(Outstanding graduate. Name: Huo Xiyi)
The victim wasn't a human
(Can see UV light that other animals can't)
but a salamander.
It can regenerate severed limbs
and see UV light.
So during the party,
it planned to cut of the power at 3PM
and prank us with its severed limbs.
The killer discovered
its prank
and used its plan
to kill it.
(Figured the murder through Tui Haowan's
regeneration ability and plan)
During the investigation,
we found the power box
and saw the label
using the UV light.
(Do not touch. Risk of electric shock)
I believe the killer swapped
the labels on the breaker,
causing the victim
(Reconstruct the murder)
to be electrocuted.
(based on breaker label
and victim notes)
After retracing the killer's actions,
I realised the note we found
in the office telling us
to hide in the locker
(Discovered more details)
was planted by the killer.
(Believed killer staged it on purpose)
Only then,
they can avoid everyone
and commit the crime.
While searching,
we found
the night vision glasses and UV light.
Since we were injected with the drug,
we began showing animal traits.
The killer used these two items.
(Rule out the two based on need)
If the killer were a dog or rabbit,
(to use the tools)
they wouldn't need the tools.
So we ruled out
Nan Shy and Ke Uh-Oh.
That left Jin and me.
Jin was the HR.
She had easier access to the boss
(Chose Jin based on access and familiarity)
and knew the company better.
So I voted for her.
(Voting window. Jin Goofy)
(Zhou Keyu player log archive)
(Profile update. Ke Uh-Oh)
(Tui Games Company
official cosplayer and sales)
(Clean record, handsome all the way)
I am player, Zhou Keyu.
In this case,
I play Tui Games Company's
official cosplayer and sales,
Ke Uh-Oh.
It was the Tui Games Company's
monthly team-building event.
I wasn't chosen last month,
but I arrived on time.
Right after finishing a ghost story,
a severed limb fell from the sky.
Ding and Ning confirmed
it was the boss, Tui Haowan's, leg.
During the investigation,
I was surprised to discover He Struggle
(After testimony and animal fur,)
also showed signs of animal behavior.
(confirmed everyone was mutating)
A lot of capybara fur.
That only strengthened my suspicion.
We were humans
penned up by Tui Haowan.
(Suspected the hidden truth
based on everyone's abnormal mutations)
We found the boss' other foot and head
in the courtyard
(Melt-Away)
as well as Melt-Away.
I believe the killer must have
(Estimated time of death)
committed the murder during the 15 minutes
(based on the timeline and burnt switch)
we hid in the locker.
He pulled it.
But there was a severed limb
in the meeting room.
(Revenge)
(Guessing the time of murder)
Did he die even earlier?
(based on the severed limb's appearance)
The man who gave the opening speech
might not have been him.
During investigation,
we arrived at the mysterious zone.
It confirmed that we were humans
(The Mirror)
turning into animals.
(confirmed them as humans)
With Bu Kakao and Tai Kule's help,
we entered the animal's world
A fox.
(Outstanding graduate. Name: Huo Xiyi)
and discovered the boss was actually a salamander.
(Can see UV light
that other animals can't)
He could also see UV light.
Catch UV light.
So the killer must have learned
about Tui Haowan's plan in advance.
(Knew victim can see UV light)
Knew it can see UV light.
(Realizing the killer
knew the victim's identity)
The victim used invisible UV markings
to mark the faulty switch.
(Exposing killer's trap)
The killer only needed to set up
(based on the breaker clues)
the switch beforehand
to complete the murder.
Switched it to the middle one.
In the courtyard,
I found the night vision glasses.
Night vision glasses.
The rabbit, Nan, and I
were both nocturnal animals.
(Nan and him have night vision)
We didn't need the glasses.
(They were ruled out)
During the discussion,
I suggested the killer must be someone
who could contact the boss
and knew the boss' murder plan.
Only then could they use
that information to kill him instead.
Among us, only Jin and He
went to his office
to submit their resignations.
They both went.
(Jin and He went to his office)
They might've seen the boss' phone.
(They had access to key information)
Following this logic,
we could narrow the suspects
to He Struggle and Jin Goofy.
(Analyzing animal traits)
But I believe
(He Struggle's motive became weaker)
since everyone gained animal traits,
capybaras would become much gentler.
So I cast my vote
for my beloved sister,
Jin Goofy.
(Voting window. Jin Goofy)
(Zhang Ruonan player log archive)
(Profile update. Nan Shy)
(Tui Games Company game designer)
(Nan Shy is really shy)
I am player, Zhang Ruonan.
In the case,
I play Tui Games Company's
game designer, Nan Shy.
Toway was 22 June
and also the company's
monthly crazy animal theme party.
We say in the meeting room
sharing ghost stories.
Suddenly, a severed leg
fell from the ceiling
with the word "revenge" written on it.
Ning Watcha and Ding Staring confirmed
that it belonged to our boss.
Did Tui Haowan,
who only just left,
(Estimating time of death from the limb)
got dismembered in such a short time?
(Questioning how he was dismembered)
Such a bizarre tragedy
actually happened here.
I found a page about a myth.
(How to break "Who can help me?" myth)
Because we couldn't find
the victim's body.
Temporarily escaped punishment.
Following the instructions on the page,
we hid in the six lockers respectively.
During the investigation,
we discovered someone
wanted revenge against humans.
Revenge.
We also learned
everyone's motives for killing
and discovered that everyone
had some animal traits.
Were we originally animals?
(Based on our mutations
and everyone's testimonies,)
(questions everyone's identities)
But we were turned into humans.
During further investigation,
we arrived at the mysterious zone.
Through the animals
living here and clues,
I concluded that our past selves
were bad people.
...doing these things.
We were the bad guys.
(Based on the poster)
So we were
(inferred the animals' revenge)
punished by the animals we once abused.
They wanted us
to experience their suffering.
Our deductions were proven correct.
Locked here.
(Input animal habitat verbally)
Through the Mirror and clues from animal world,
(Access local human punishment records)
Human punishment records.
we confirmed we were humans
(The punishment records)
who had abused animals.
(confirmed why there were brought there)
...to hell.
Later, we found a saw
in Tui Haowan's box.
(Based on the bloodstains,)
It must have been used
(inferred how the saw was used)
to cut his limbs off.
(I can use my trait to create fear)
Tui Haowan had created a murder plan
(Once they're in, I can get rid of them)
to take revenge on humans.
(Foolish, cruel humans. Just you wait)
He also found accomplices
Help me scare them.
I remember the six lockers we hid in
could be accessed freely.
(Estimate time of crime)
The killer likely
(based on locker access)
used that time to leave and commit murder.
We concluded the killer
knew about Tui Haowan's plan,
then changed the UV label on the breaker
to kill him instead.
We then found a pair
of night vision glasses in the courtyard.
Both dogs and rabbits
can see in the night.
Night vision.
(Checking unique animal traits)
So when moving in darkness,
(Further narrowing the suspects)
they wouldn't need it.
(unable to rule out He Struggle)
Capybara traits were harder to identify.
(He Struggle still a suspect)
You don't believe me.
The killer used night vision glasses
and UV light.
So I thought He Struggle was
the most suspicious.
He may also have wanted
(Analyzing killer's motive)
to leave the company with me.
(Feels He Struggle
has stronger motive to leave)
So I voted for him.
(Voting window)
(Liu Yuning player log archive)
(Profile update. Ning Watcha)
(Tui Games Company janitor)
(Love playing games and became a janitor
at a game company)
I am player, Liu Yuning.
In this case,
I play Tui Games Company's
janitor, Ning Watcha.
On my second day after joining,
I took part in the company's
monthly
crazy animal theme party.
Ding Staring and I hosted
the ghost story sharing session.
But suddenly,
a severed limb fell from the sky.
Then
a voice asked us to find its body.
(Sudden appearance of severed limb
matches the ghost story)
It matched
the ghost story I was telling.
It actually came true.
Because the severed limb
had a burn mark left on the boss
by Ding Staring.
Isn't this the boss' leg?
That's right. It is.
(Confirmed victim's identity)
It proved that it belongs to our boss.
(based on the injury)
Since Ding and I
stayed together
since joining the company,
Since you two have an alibi,
we both became the detectives.
it's all yours now.
Alright.
We then searched
the suspects' rooms.
We discovered Jin Goofy, He Struggle,
Nin Shy, and Ke Uh-oh
were all bullied by the boss at work.
They couldn't escape.
Dizzy.
Sent back to the office.
(Combining the evidence gathered)
So they all had motives to kill.
(Found out everyone had a motive)
What was more unbelievable was
that we might all
actually be animals.
The scattered limbs pieced together
to form a message.
This is a revenge against humans.
(Formed a message using the writing on the limbs)
This showed that one of the animals
(Killer wants to take revenge against victim)
launched revenge against the human boss.
But a question remain.
From the moment the boss
finished his opening speech and left,
until the severed limb
appeared before us,
none of us had acted alone.
(No one left their sight,
making the timeline impossible to trace)
So how did the killer do it?
Could it be that the killer
was not among those four people?
(Everyone lacked opportunity to commit the crime)
Or perhaps there was an accomplice?
(Suspecting an accomplice)
An accomplice, right?
We then entered the mysterious zone.
There, we witnessed animals
taking revenge on humans
who abused them.
However, the six of us were detected
to be humans, not animals.
You are humans.
Just as we were about to be captured,
the boss' secretary, Bu Kakao,
brought us to a new space.
There, we discovered,
the company was actually a human prison.
It was a place established by
higher-dimensional beings
to punish humans who abused animals.
Yes.
I suddenly realized
that Tui Haowan could be an animal.
(Combine clues and reason
about Tui Haowan's true identity)
(Outstanding graduate. Name: Huo Xiyi)
Sure enough, we learned
(Can see UV light that other animals can't)
it was a salamander.
Its special ability
Its special ability was regeneration.
is to grow back severed limbs.
The severed limbs were actually
cut off by Tui Haowan himself
(Revealing the truth of the revenge)
and placed around the area.
(based on the victim's animal trait and plan)
Lure them to the mysterious zone.
It was
to lure us into the mysterious zone
and kill us.
The killer, however,
used Tui Haowan's plan
and turned it against him.
They first moved the labels
causing him to be electrocuted
when he pulled the breaker.
(Melt-Away)
Then during the 15 minutes of darkness,
(Reconstructing the murder)
they dissolved his body in the vat.
(based on clues gathered)
We were all injected with the drug
and gradually gained animal traits.
(Do not touch. Risk of electric shock)
The killer
used night vision glasses and UV light.
If a dog or rabbit
committed the murder,
they didn't need
to use both tools.
The killer used these two tools.
(Based on murder tools,)
so we could eliminate Ke and Nan.
(eliminate Ke and Nan )
Don't need these.
The killer must have known
about Tui Haowan's plan.
Among Jin and He,
Jin can get close to the boss easier.
I am usually with him.
She was more likely
to see the boss' phone and notebook.
So I voted for Jin Goofy.
(Voting window)
(TNT, Ding Chengxin player log archive)
(Profile update. Ding Staring)
(Tui Games Company security)
(Snail guard)
I am player, Ding Chengxin.
In this case,
I play Tui Games Company's security,
Ding Staring.
I am also the detective of the case.
During the company's monthly
crazy animal theme party,
the boss, Tui Haowan, gave a speech
and announced that the event
had officially begun.
Then he left.
Soon after, the power
went out during the event,
and strange things started happening.
(Revenge)
Tui Haowan's severed limbs
(Against humans)
began appearing throughout the company.
We first found his right leg.
Finally, while searching the courtyard,
we discovered the boss' head
on the lid of a vat
that was filled with bloody water
(Deducted killer's process using Melt-Away)
which was his dissolved body.
The backup power supply
would only activate 15 minutes
after a blackout.
At first glance,
it seemed the killer had
to complete the murder, dismemberment,
and move the body parts
(Reviewing timeline)
within 15 minutes.
(Questions whether the crime was possible)
It was almost impossible.
During the first discussion,
I remembered the boss's head
looked more like he
had been electrocuted.
I immediately presented my theory.
(Based on the black marks on victim's face,)
Burned. It was black.
(assuming the cause of death
was electrocution)
Then we entered the mysterious zone.
There, we witnessed
animals taking revenge on humans.
Based on the clues, I guessed
that because we had
abused animals before,
Abuse.
someone had turned us into animals as well
(Using photos to determine victim's goal)
and taken revenge against us,
(Suspected victim used drugs to carry out revenge)
Making us experience their suffering.
Experience their suffering.
Through the Mirror,
it was also confirmed
that the six of us were humans.
You are humans.
With the help of Bu Kakao and Tai Kule,
we escaped
and arrived at animal world.
So beautiful.
(Confirmed victim's revenge motive)
There, we confirmed our suspicion.
(based on the posters)
We also learned that Tui Haowan
(Outstanding graduate. Name: Huo Xiyi)
was actually an animal.
(Can see UV light
that other animals can't)
According to the life monitor,
Tui Haowan's heartbeat
only stopped at 3PM.
Considering its original animal trait
as a salamander,
he could regenerate limbs.
(Victim died after severing his limb)
I realized that it cut off its limbs
(Uncovered victim's plan to create fear)
to spread fear.
The killer then used
the victim's plan
to create a fake death scene.
(Guesses killer's purpose)
they deliberately disrupted our judgment
(through victim's ability)
of the time of death.
As we investigated more,
we realized Tui Haowan wanted Bu Kakao
to use UV light
to leave a mark on the breaker
(Do not touch. Risk of electric shock)
so he could scare us during the blackout.
But someone learned
of its plan beforehand
and used the mechanism
to kill it instead.
(Using the misplaced break label
to reconstruct the murder)
So in my thinking,
the killer had to know
Tui Haowan's breaker plan.
Pull the main breaker down.
(Sorting through clues to figure the crime)
Can enter the boss' office,
(Special spectral light)
find the spectral light,
and the breaker key.
But we found the night vision glasses.
Based on animal traits,
we ruled out
Ke Uh-oh who can see UV light
and Nan Shy who can see in the dark.
(Narrow down suspects
based on murder tools)
I was more suspicious of Jin Goofy
because beluga whales
are very smart creatures.
Highly intelligent.
They are capable of planning a crime.
Secondly, her younger brother
was also harmed by Tui Haowan.
Her motive was the strongest.
(Combining motive and learning victim's plan)
She also had enough time
(Finally locking down on suspect)
to approach Tui Haowan's room,
The boss' room.
So I voted for Jin Goofy.
(Voting window. Jin Goofy)
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Viewing Calendar)
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪